[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "RB", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "RB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VB", "IN", "EX", "MD", "VB", "NN", "RB", "RB", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 22, "question": "Dana are we seeing a puff of political white smoke?", "question_tokens": ["Dana", "are", "we", "seeing", "a", "puff", "of", "political", "white", "smoke", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 23, "answer": "I wouldn't call it white smoke yet but we're definitely at the point where we could at least look up to the tower and see if there could be smoke anytime soon, which is a lot further away than we were just a few hours ago, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "n't", "call", "it", "white", "smoke", "yet", "but", "we", "'re", "definitely", "at", "the", "point", "where", "we", "could", "at", "least", "look", "up", "to", "the", "tower", "and", "see", "if", "there", "could", "be", "smoke", "anytime", "soon", ",", "which", "is", "a", "lot", "further", "away", "than", "we", "were", "just", "a", "few", "hours", "ago", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 28, "question": "Did you clash with the President is that fair to say?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "clash", "with", "the", "President", "is", "that", "fair", "to", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 29, "answer": "I did.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "How did you - What did you clash over, was it about how to reopen the government and went to do it?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "-", "What", "did", "you", "clash", "over", ",", "was", "it", "about", "how", "to", "reopen", "the", "government", "and", "went", "to", "do", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", ":", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "If you focus on things that might be clashing, those are probably be in a book someday.", "answer_tokens": ["If", "you", "focus", "on", "things", "that", "might", "be", "clashing", ",", "those", "are", "probably", "be", "in", "a", "book", "someday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 38, "question": "I hear that Joe Biden is still trapped inside the White House is that a good sign the great deal maker hasn't emerged yet?", "question_tokens": ["I", "hear", "that", "Joe", "Biden", "is", "still", "trapped", "inside", "the", "White", "House", "is", "that", "a", "good", "sign", "the", "great", "deal", "maker", "has", "n't", "emerged", "yet", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 39, "answer": "I think that is a good sign, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "is", "a", "good", "sign", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "PERSON": ["Joe Biden"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "Let's start with you Jim Himes, what are you sensing?", "question_tokens": ["Let", "'s", "start", "with", "you", "Jim", "Himes", ",", "what", "are", "you", "sensing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, I'm encouraged.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "encouraged", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim Himes"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jim"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 79, "question": "How do you see the deal which is probably pretty close to being done now actually being completed?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "see", "the", "deal", "which", "is", "probably", "pretty", "close", "to", "being", "done", "now", "actually", "being", "completed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 80, "answer": "Well I agree very much actually with what Jim had to say.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "agree", "very", "much", "actually", "with", "what", "Jim", "had", "to", "say", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump", "Donald Trump"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "NN", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 93, "question": "Have you got anything to say that this doesn't look very good the way this is all played out?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "got", "anything", "to", "say", "that", "this", "does", "n't", "look", "very", "good", "the", "way", "this", "is", "all", "played", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 94, "answer": "Well, first of all, I never sort about looked to Donald Trump for what is true and good in this world, but also look, Donald Trump in his business when he doesn't like how something is going, he can just do as he does and say you're fired.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "never", "sort", "about", "looked", "to", "Donald", "Trump", "for", "what", "is", "true", "and", "good", "in", "this", "world", ",", "but", "also", "look", ",", "Donald", "Trump", "in", "his", "business", "when", "he", "does", "n't", "like", "how", "something", "is", "going", ",", "he", "can", "just", "do", "as", "he", "does", "and", "say", "you", "'re", "fired", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 102, "question": "Tom Cole, do you think that Donald Trump is a force of evil in this world as Mr. Himes seemed to be implying at?", "question_tokens": ["Tom", "Cole", ",", "do", "you", "think", "that", "Donald", "Trump", "is", "a", "force", "of", "evil", "in", "this", "world", "as", "Mr.", "Himes", "seemed", "to", "be", "implying", "at", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 103, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Tom Cole", "Donald Trump", "Mr. Himes"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJR", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 116, "question": "From the default?", "question_tokens": ["From", "the", "default", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 117, "answer": "Hold it let me answer you a question.", "answer_tokens": ["Hold", "it", "let", "me", "answer", "you", "a", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 145, "question": "Now look, you are the man to talk to you here, where is this deal in the devil of the detail going to get done do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Now", "look", ",", "you", "are", "the", "man", "to", "talk", "to", "you", "here", ",", "where", "is", "this", "deal", "in", "the", "devil", "of", "the", "detail", "going", "to", "get", "done", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 146, "answer": "Well that's a good question and I would still say if.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "that", "'s", "a", "good", "question", "and", "I", "would", "still", "say", "if", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 161, "question": "Is that your take on it?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "your", "take", "on", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 162, "answer": "Yes, you just had a great conversation with a Democrat and a Republican.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "you", "just", "had", "a", "great", "conversation", "with", "a", "Democrat", "and", "a", "Republican", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John King"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 174, "question": "The question is how high of a political price did they pay to get them?", "question_tokens": ["The", "question", "is", "how", "high", "of", "a", "political", "price", "did", "they", "pay", "to", "get", "them", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 175, "answer": "(inaudible) stuff, John King, thank you very much indeed.", "answer_tokens": ["(", "inaudible", ")", "stuff", ",", "John", "King", ",", "thank", "you", "very", "much", "indeed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Watergate Committee"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 184, "question": "What is your take with all your experience at this?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "take", "with", "all", "your", "experience", "at", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 185, "answer": "Well, going back to my experience on the Watergate Committee which you referenced.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "going", "back", "to", "my", "experience", "on", "the", "Watergate", "Committee", "which", "you", "referenced", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Nixon"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WDT", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 217, "question": "Have you ever known Washington be so partisan vicious frankly, is this how'd become?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "ever", "known", "Washington", "be", "so", "partisan", "vicious", "frankly", ",", "is", "this", "how", "'d", "become", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "WRB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 218, "answer": "It started actually, my recollection is subsequent to the Nixon effort which ended up the way it ended up with his resignation.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "started", "actually", ",", "my", "recollection", "is", "subsequent", "to", "the", "Nixon", "effort", "which", "ended", "up", "the", "way", "it", "ended", "up", "with", "his", "resignation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Now, your client has been charged of reckless driving and unlawful imprisonment, what is your position with him?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "your", "client", "has", "been", "charged", "of", "reckless", "driving", "and", "unlawful", "imprisonment", ",", "what", "is", "your", "position", "with", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "VBG", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Well, my position with my client is that he committed no crime.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "my", "position", "with", "my", "client", "is", "that", "he", "committed", "no", "crime", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WRB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "Why is he looking behind him to make a lane change?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "he", "looking", "behind", "him", "to", "make", "a", "lane", "change", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "Well, he's on a motorcycle, you got to understand he's not in a motor vehicle where, you know, you're looking at your side mirrors and you feel a little bit more comfortable, safer.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "he", "'s", "on", "a", "motorcycle", ",", "you", "got", "to", "understand", "he", "'s", "not", "in", "a", "motor", "vehicle", "where", ",", "you", "know", ",", "you", "'re", "looking", "at", "your", "side", "mirrors", "and", "you", "feel", "a", "little", "bit", "more", "comfortable", ",", "safer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Benjamin"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", ":", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "CC", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "What do you make of this defense of Mr. Cruz?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "defense", "of", "Mr.", "Cruz", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "Well, with all (ph), obviously, I'm not defending or speaking to Benjamin's client where he is, but from a video standpoint, you know, I just don't buy it, I mean, he wasn't making a lane change.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "with", "all", "(", "ph", ")", ",", "obviously", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "defending", "or", "speaking", "to", "Benjamin", "'s", "client", "where", "he", "is", ",", "but", "from", "a", "video", "standpoint", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "just", "do", "n't", "buy", "it", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "he", "was", "n't", "making", "a", "lane", "change", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Cruz"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Cruz"], "LOCATION": ["Manhattan"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", ":", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "WDT", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ":", "NN", "VBG", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "RP", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 270, "question": "What do you think he's doing?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "he", "'s", "doing", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 271, "answer": "They were surrounding that vehicle obviously -- look, don't forget this has been precipitated by 200 911 calls that these guys are riding, terrorizing the West Side Highway in Manhattan, one of the busiest streets in the country in that sort of pot-like (ph) mentality surrounding vehicles that got in their way and that's exactly what they did here and what I believe Mr. Cruz was doing was basically going to slow this guy down and basically surround these guys which they eventually did.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "were", "surrounding", "that", "vehicle", "obviously", "--", "look", ",", "do", "n't", "forget", "this", "has", "been", "precipitated", "by", "200", "911", "calls", "that", "these", "guys", "are", "riding", ",", "terrorizing", "the", "West", "Side", "Highway", "in", "Manhattan", ",", "one", "of", "the", "busiest", "streets", "in", "the", "country", "in", "that", "sort", "of", "pot-like", "(", "ph", ")", "mentality", "surrounding", "vehicles", "that", "got", "in", "their", "way", "and", "that", "'s", "exactly", "what", "they", "did", "here", "and", "what", "I", "believe", "Mr.", "Cruz", "was", "doing", "was", "basically", "going", "to", "slow", "this", "guy", "down", "and", "basically", "surround", "these", "guys", "which", "they", "eventually", "did", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "CC", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 276, "question": "He raised -- and we've all seen the video, but do you think that there is a proper defense for what he did?", "question_tokens": ["He", "raised", "--", "and", "we", "'ve", "all", "seen", "the", "video", ",", "but", "do", "you", "think", "that", "there", "is", "a", "proper", "defense", "for", "what", "he", "did", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 277, "answer": "Now is your proper defense is there is clearly, in my opinion, no wrong turn, this is a tragedy what we're seeing here but what I'll say is this, the law is if you reasonably believe that he was in danger when he acted then he is good to go.", "answer_tokens": ["Now", "is", "your", "proper", "defense", "is", "there", "is", "clearly", ",", "in", "my", "opinion", ",", "no", "wrong", "turn", ",", "this", "is", "a", "tragedy", "what", "we", "'re", "seeing", "here", "but", "what", "I", "'ll", "say", "is", "this", ",", "the", "law", "is", "if", "you", "reasonably", "believe", "that", "he", "was", "in", "danger", "when", "he", "acted", "then", "he", "is", "good", "to", "go", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "You'll think of the family?", "question_tokens": ["You", "'ll", "think", "of", "the", "family", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "ORGAN: Wife, children?", "question_tokens": ["ORGAN", ":", "Wife", ",", "children", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "I have children.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "have", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERCENT": ["99 percent"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "CD", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "First of all, what is his condition today?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "what", "is", "his", "condition", "today", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, unfortunately the doctors have told him that he has 99 percent probability of never being able to walk again.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "unfortunately", "the", "doctors", "have", "told", "him", "that", "he", "has", "99", "percent", "probability", "of", "never", "being", "able", "to", "walk", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 370, "question": "Donald Trump, if you were the CEO of Washington Incorporated right now, how many times would you been saying, \"You're fired\" in the last few weeks?", "question_tokens": ["Donald", "Trump", ",", "if", "you", "were", "the", "CEO", "of", "Washington", "Incorporated", "right", "now", ",", "how", "many", "times", "would", "you", "been", "saying", ",", "``", "You", "'re", "fired", "''", "in", "the", "last", "few", "weeks", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBG", ",", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "''", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 371, "answer": "Well, probably a lot but they really have to learn to get along.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "probably", "a", "lot", "but", "they", "really", "have", "to", "learn", "to", "get", "along", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Donald Trump"], "LOCATION": ["Washington"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 388, "question": "As a top businessman, what do you think of that?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "top", "businessman", ",", "what", "do", "you", "think", "of", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 389, "answer": "Well, nobody knows.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "nobody", "knows", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "Can you even believe that figure?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "even", "believe", "that", "figure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "The laugh of the (inaudible) because actually they have a position of strength don't they?", "question_tokens": ["The", "laugh", "of", "the", "(", "inaudible", ")", "because", "actually", "they", "have", "a", "position", "of", "strength", "do", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "They have played us.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "have", "played", "us", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBG", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 457, "question": "How did you feel when you heard the death payments to the widows and families of dead servicemen and women in the American military were not going to be paid?", "question_tokens": ["How", "did", "you", "feel", "when", "you", "heard", "the", "death", "payments", "to", "the", "widows", "and", "families", "of", "dead", "servicemen", "and", "women", "in", "the", "American", "military", "were", "not", "going", "to", "be", "paid", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 458, "answer": "Well, I thought it was one of the most outrageous things I've ever heard and I've been doing this for a quite a while.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "one", "of", "the", "most", "outrageous", "things", "I", "'ve", "ever", "heard", "and", "I", "'ve", "been", "doing", "this", "for", "a", "quite", "a", "while", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 470, "question": "How these guys can get together and do better business?", "question_tokens": ["How", "these", "guys", "can", "get", "together", "and", "do", "better", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 471, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 479, "question": "What advice can you give about the arts of doing a deal, of doing business?", "question_tokens": ["What", "advice", "can", "you", "give", "about", "the", "arts", "of", "doing", "a", "deal", ",", "of", "doing", "business", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 480, "answer": "Well, I think one of the biggest problem is that they don't like each other.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "one", "of", "the", "biggest", "problem", "is", "that", "they", "do", "n't", "like", "each", "other", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 506, "question": "Is that a problem, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "a", "problem", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 507, "answer": "I think it is, because I don't think he's a natural dealmaker.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "is", ",", "because", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "he", "'s", "a", "natural", "dealmaker", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 526, "question": "You go along with that?", "question_tokens": ["You", "go", "along", "with", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 527, "answer": "Well, I do look.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "look", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 541, "question": "What do you do about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 542, "answer": "Well, and again, it's jobs.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "and", "again", ",", "it", "'s", "jobs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ":"], "qSentId": 581, "question": "How do you feel as an American?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "feel", "as", "an", "American", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Yes ...", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "..."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "WRB", "DT", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBD", "VBN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "CC", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 585, "question": "As an American, do you not feel embarrassed when this kind of thing happens?", "question_tokens": ["As", "an", "American", ",", "do", "you", "not", "feel", "embarrassed", "when", "this", "kind", "of", "thing", "happens", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 586, "answer": "Well, you know, when the Statue of Liberty, Piers, was closed and they announced and everything, I thought it was very bad.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "when", "the", "Statue", "of", "Liberty", ",", "Piers", ",", "was", "closed", "and", "they", "announced", "and", "everything", ",", "I", "thought", "it", "was", "very", "bad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 597, "question": "Donald, I like just to give an immediate reaction to all the following names with your apprentice, (inaudible), if they were in the board room, what you would say?", "question_tokens": ["Donald", ",", "I", "like", "just", "to", "give", "an", "immediate", "reaction", "to", "all", "the", "following", "names", "with", "your", "apprentice", ",", "(", "inaudible", ")", ",", "if", "they", "were", "in", "the", "board", "room", ",", "what", "you", "would", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", ":", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 598, "answer": "OK.", "answer_tokens": ["OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 603, "question": "Hired or fired?", "question_tokens": ["Hired", "or", "fired", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "CC", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 604, "answer": "OH, I'd hire, absolutely.", "answer_tokens": ["OH", ",", "I", "'d", "hire", ",", "absolutely", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 618, "question": "Would you hire him?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "hire", "him", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 619, "answer": "Well, I'd hire him.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'d", "hire", "him", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 621, "question": "ObamaCare?", "question_tokens": ["ObamaCare", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 622, "answer": "ObamaCare is a disaster.", "answer_tokens": ["ObamaCare", "is", "a", "disaster", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "131010pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "."], "qSentId": 637, "question": "Has she taught you how to twerk?", "question_tokens": ["Has", "she", "taught", "you", "how", "to", "twerk", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "WRB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 638, "answer": "I don't know if I can't do it like her.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "know", "if", "I", "ca", "n't", "do", "it", "like", "her", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]